How does retroactivity work?	
  The retroactivity feature ensures that employees created in the tool after their company entry date and during the rule execution period are taken into account.
  Conditions:
  With regard to this functionality, particularly for Onboarding rules, there are three conditions (in addition to the employee meeting the KPP filters, etc.):
  The employee must have a company or group entry date within the set timeframe (D-31 maximum).
  The employee must have a company or group entry date after the date on which the rule is first executed.
  The employee's account must have been created after the rule's first execution date.

How do the prerequisites work within Training Match?	
  It is possible to define prerequisites in the cycle at the level of steps or training courses.
  All courses in the step defined as a prerequisite must be completed before courses in subsequent steps can be carried out.


Can we manage certification renewals with Training Match?	
  Yes, this is possible.
  Unlike other types of rules, which can be used to generate registrations, requests or suggestions for training cycles, certification renewal only allows automatic registrations for training courses.
  Once your rule has been configured, Training Match will identify each day the people with the certification to be renewed who are part of the target population, then automatically register them in the appropriate training session."
  An employee was not registered by Training Match when he should have been. Why ?	"You've created and started your Training Match rule with the expected result of registration, but your collaborator hasn't been registered.
  Here's what you need to check to make sure the registration is completed:
  1. Check that the collaborator is present in the Simulation
  2. Check that the Training Match batch is activated (please contact our Customer Care team for this)
  3. The collaborator cannot be registered at the moment because one or more of the following conditions are missing: Session active (not in a final state), Session ending after the arrival date if ""session in progress"" in the rule OR session starting after the arrival date, Session starting after the deadline defined in the cycle (applied to the arrival date), Session starting after the end of the prerequisite action sessions (defined in the cycle), Session with space available, Session for which the collaborator meets the enrolment criteria (key properties), Session for which the collaborator is available (no synchronous training at the same time).

Can I delete a Training Match rule?	
  Yes, if the rule concerned is in draft state OR is active but not executed.
  Training Match rules already executed cannot be deleted, only archived."
  Can I modify a Training Match rule after activation?	"Once your Training Match rule has been activated, it can no longer be modified. If you wish to make changes, you must duplicate it and deactivate the old rule.
  The new duplicated rule will then be in draft form, and you will be able to modify it."
  Can I use Training Match to manage mass registration for training courses?	Training Match is not designed to manage large volumes of registrations, but to automate recurring registrations. We therefore advise you against using it for this purpose.
  A rule has been created with an effective date of today, but the target population has not yet been registered. Why has this happened?	"Training Match runs every day at around 5:00 a.m. (GMT), by default.
  If you activate a rule on the same day as its execution start date, and the daily execution time has passed, you'll have to wait until the following morning to see the first registrations made.

How do I display the ""Their training"" widget?
  Your managers can keep track of their employees' training requests and registrations from the ""Their training"" widget.
  This widget is available from the home page by switching from the ""My Space"" view to ""My Team"" and/or ""My N-1"".
  This widget is only available to managers in the ""My Team"" and ""My N-1"" views.
  It will not be available for the ""My perimeter"" view.
  For it to be displayed, the following conditions must be met: 
    Have the right to ""View the ""Registration"" tab"" to see the ""Registration"" tab, 
    Have the right to ""View the ""Training requests"" tab"" to see the ""Requests"" tab, 
    Have authorization for the employee on the ""Collab. profile"" and ""FO training"" analysis modules.

How can I hide requirements and registrations in the ""My training"" widget?
  You can configure the display of requests and registrations in the ""My training"" widget from Intelligence > Object settings > Registrations (or Training requests) > Status types.
  These screens let you configure:
  - for registrations: whether a registration should be visible according to its status,
  - for request: whether a request should be visible according to its status and source."
  How do I change the layout of my widgets?	"From the My Talentsoft page, you can change the order of the widgets to suit your needs. To do so, click on the ""Manage"" pencil icon on your home page.
  Please note that the widget order cannot be set by default for all collaborators. In fact, this feature means that each collaborator is free to modify the order of widgets on his or her space as he or she sees fit.

How can I remove the ""Text 1"" field from the training requests interface in the My/Their Training Widgets?	
  From the ""My training"" and ""Their training"" widgets, when you select a training request, the details display the ""Text 1"" field, notably used when requesting training via form (Performance and Skills modules).
  This customizable field had been requested by many customers during the widget's co-construction phase, and was therefore displayed by default in the requirements detail.
  If you no longer wish to display the ""Text1"" field in the widget's training requirements, please request it by support ticket, using the following procedure:
  Company characteristic ""DisplayRequirementText1InWidget"" to be set to ""False"".

What is the order of display of registrations on my ""My courses"" widget, and can it be configured?	
  Registrations for current sessions are displayed according to the session end date.
  For example, a registration for a session ending on July 15 of the current year will be placed before a registration for a session ending on October 30."
  "When impersonating an employee's identity, the ""My training"" and ""Their training"" widgets do not appear. Why not?"	"The ""My training"" and ""Their training"" widgets do not appear when impersonating an employee, for reasons of compliance with fundamental RGPD principles. Given the principles of default data protection and minimization, this access is not justified."
  "When I log in, why do I see the message ""Authentication failed""?"	Please ensure that you have an active LMS account. If you do, please ensure that you have correctly entered your log-in details (username and password). Take care, these details are case-sensitive.
  Can I log into the LMS application using a QR code or a direct link?	"Yes: the QR Code is available in the ""My training"" area of the LMS, as long as:
  - session separators are active: Administration > Display > Display options > Display a session separator on the course page > Yes
  - the session must be set up to allow downloading to the LMS app: from the page for the session in question > ""Information"" section > ""Modify"" button > activate the setting ""Download session content to the LMS app""
  This QR Code can also be received by sending an email suing the ""APP_LMS_CONNECT"" template.
  Furthermore, this email template includes a link that, once used on the recipient's phone, opens the LMS Application (if it has been installed) and logs in automatically.

Can I expand a training unit screen on the LMS mobile application?	
  It is not currently possible to zoom in this way. If a training session is to be followed on mobile devices, we encourage you to size the elements (text, images, videos, etc.) accordingly so as not to lose readability.
  How do I download an e-learning session to the LMS mobile application or delete a session from the application?	"This can be done when you log into the application with a Trainee profile (or similar). On the home page of the application, open the page ""Download and play your courses offline"". On this page, you will find all of the content that you have authorisation to download to read offline.
  To delete a downloaded training session, go to the ""Settings"" area within the application (settings icon, top right), then open the ""Storage management"" page and use the ""Delete"" button at the bottom of the screen to delete content from your telephone."
  
Why are the results for a Trainee who has approved their training on the LMS application not visible?	
  This Trainee probably completed their training offline after downloading the content to their telephone using the application. 
  The application must be connected to the internet to enable the results to be sent to the LMS.
  
How can I exceed the 32 MB limit when importing files into the LCMS online editor?	
  A maximum file size of 32 MB is permitted when uploading videos when setting up an activity within the LCMS online editor.
  However, it is possible to integrate larger videos as follows: from your Library, create a new ""Video"" document. The maximum file size for files imported in this way is between 1 and 4 GB (depending on your LCMS settings). 
  Once your LU has been created, there may be a delay in processing your imported file prior to it becoming usable. When your video file is visible in the ""Media"" tab, it can be used as normal.
  Once your video has been imported as a new document and processed, you can integrate it into your activity using the editor by selecting from ""Project media""."
  
How do I add or delete a folder in the Library for my LCMS project?	
  To add a folder, go to the Documents and Course tabs in your Library. Click on New > New folder.
  To delete a folder, select it, then click on the arrow to the right of the title in the breadcrumb trail. This displays options for editing and deleting this folder.
  CAUTION: deleting a folder also deletes the documents that it contains.
  
How do I reuse a TvLearn animation in multiple training units?	
  A TvLearn produced using the online LCMS creates a separate LU. Therefore, you cannot integrate a LU in another LU. In contrast, you can extract the animation from the TvLearn LU to integrate it into another LU. To do this, go to the TvLearn LU file, click on the menu (to the right of the ""Publish"" button), then ""Extract an animation"" and select the corresponding animation.
  This is then made available as an independent object in your Project Library and can be reused within any E-learning type LU as follows: in the online editor, add an Animation or TvLearn activity and use the import project animation function to integrate the previously created document."
  
Is it possible to export a TvLearn in video format (mp4)?	
  At this time, this type of export is not possible. However, you can reuse the TvLearn animation in other LU.
  
Why can I not open a learning unit downloaded from the LCMS in the ""Web export"" format?
  A web export is intended to be used online and, therefore, should be stored on a web server in advance.
  If you open  this content on your computer using an index.html file, it will probably be blocked by your browser (for security reasons). 
  Therefore, it is recommended that the web export should be stored on a web server and opened using the latter or, if the export should be used locally to prioritise a CDRom type export which integrates an executable file (.exe), 
  enabling it be used on a computer.
  
Why is the message ""It is not possible to connect to the LMS. Please check the settings"" displayed when publishing or reviewing on the LCMS?
	In the first place, please check that your LCMS platform is connected to the expected to the expected LMS platform by accessing the screen available via Administration > LMS Configuration.
  If the expected LMS is there, check that the account you use on the LCMS has the same login as an existing LMS account and has adequate rights for at least one of the associated profiles. The rights in question are: 
  - edit a course,
  - import a course.
  Otherwise, you must create an account on the LMS so that the connection can be established between the platforms and enable you to publish.
  If the warning still appears despite these checks, please contact Talentsoft Customer Care."
  
What is the purpose of the CSV import function that is available on the LCMS online editor?	
  CSV importing into the LCMS online editor enables quizzes to be generated without having to use the Production LCMS application. This allows you to create three types of activities: MCQ, SCQ and text entry. 
  Refer to the sample file available for download for further information about the structure of the file to be completed.
  Above all, this import facilitates the creation of questionnaires, however, it does not replace the settings for each activity (for example: number of attempts, corrections, etc.).
  
Should I manage (create, modify) my e-learning content on the LCMS?	
  As far as possible, create your LU and your courses using your LCMS, if you have this platform. 
  This enables you to save your work and to reuse it easily later on. 
  You also have features such as review (archiving changes made to content and the option of restoring an earlier version of a LU), test, etc. Finally, you have a larger file size limit (up to 4 GB per file),
  which enables you to put any sort of content online, unlike the LMS, which has a limit of 32 MB (which can be avoided by importing from a FTP server).
  
How can I get more settings on the LCMS online editor?	
  For this, activate advanced editing mode. This editing mode enables you to use a greater number of settings to adapt your content to your requirements. 
  You can activate this mode via the menu at the top right of the online editor.
  
Can I install the Production LCMS application on a computer other than my work computer?	
  The Production LCMS application can be installed on any terminal (professional, personal, etc.) provided that it meets the technical requirements, available on the Talentsoft Community. 
  Note that the Production LCMS application only works in a Windows environment.
  You can download the executable file for Production LCMS from the Web LCMS: top right menu > Tools > Install the app."
  
How do I update a LU without losing results (tracking)? 	
  If you want to update a LU without impacting the tracking that has already been saved, it is recommended:
  - not to change the structure of your module: no pages or activities should change position (nor should any pages be added, deleted or moved),
  - not to change the exercise types,
  - not to amend the titles of questions or the content of each exercise.
  
Why does a TvLearn not retain the media and animations from the PowerPoint file?	
  The purpose of the TvLearn functionality is to convert the Powerpoint slides into images. 
  Therefore, the animations and media are not retained.
  
Which e-learning standards are supported by the LCMS and LMS platforms?	
  Our platforms support SCORM 1.2, SCORM 2004 3rd edition and AICC 3.5. 
  Content produced using other standards (xAPI) or exported in other formats (.story files, for example) cannot be used.

Can I change the graphic design of the LCMS?	
  These changes require the appropriate tools and/or knowledge. 
  This can be done either by Talentsoft as part of the Content+ type Advanced Services or by any other supplier with the necessary technical know-how to perform such a task.
  
Can I save Tutorials (screen recording) through the Web LCMS?	
  Currently the online LCMS does not allow tutorials to be saved. Therefore, you should use the Production LCMS application to record then save online. 
  After this, you can use the animation on the Web LCMS by integrating it into a LU via an ""Animation"" type activity.
  
Why can I not integrate a video file that I have imported into the LCMS into a learning unit?	
  Importing a video into the Web LCMS is followed by processing in order to make it possible to use the file on the platform. 
  Therefore, it may be that the video file is only available for use several minutes after being imported. 
  One method of checking the availability of a file is to view the ""Media"" tab in the Library: if your file is there, it can be used. 
  If it is not there, you must wait for it to be processed.
  
Can I record more than 15 minutes using TvLearn on the Web LCMS?	
  Currently, the maximum recording period for a TvLearn is 15 minutes. 
  The user receives a notification one minute prior to the end of the recording which ends automatically after 15 minutes.
  
I cannot log into my account using the Production LCMS application (ECMG).	
  In the first place, please check that the LCMS link used is in the following format: https://xxxxx.e-learning-suite.com.
  Then check that you are using the correct login and password. 
  If necessary, you can reset your password by clicking on ""Forgotten password?"" on the LCMS login page. You will need your email address and your login.
  
How do I create multilingual learning units with the LCMS?	
  You can produce multilingual resources by using the Production LCMS application (ECMG). 
  Below you will find documentation describing this feature.
  Please note: currently, any multilingual LU should only be edited with the Production LCMS. Currently, the Web LCMS cannot handle this content.
  
Why are some templates absent from the Web LCMS?	
  It is not possible to use all templates in the online editor. 
  Some templates are reserved exclusively for the production tool because they are quite old and, for the most part, contain Flash animations that are not compatible with the Web LCMS (and that are no longer compatible with most browsers). 
  As part of work on the online editor, some templates may, in the future, be updated and made available again through the online editor of the Web LCMS.
  
How can I import/export multiple documents at the same time using my Web LCMS?	
  You can export multiple LUs from a LCMS using the Library, for example, to save them on your computer or to move them to a different LCMS platform.
  To do this, in your Library, select the LUs to be exported then click on the ""Move/Export"" button. 
  In this way, you can download an archive named after the original project for the LUs selected and containing them.
  To import it into a different LCMS, begin the creation of a new document of the ""Multiple documents"" type and select the previously downloaded archive. 
  At the end of the process, a new folder will be created in your Library, enabling you to view and use this content.

How can I edit a learning unit marked as ""Being edited by…""?
    This message can be deactivated in three ways:
      - this message is generally displayed because the LU is being edited using a user's Production LCMS application. 
        This person must save the LU online to make it available for use on the Web LCMS again,
      - you can unlock the LU by going to the file (on the Web LCMS) then by opening the action menu and clicking on ""Unlock the module"". 
        Please note that any changes to the LU not saved online are lost,
      - you can also duplicate the LU if you do not want to unlock it. 
        In this way, you will duplicate the latest update available from the root of the LCMS project.
    PLEASE NOTE: exiting the LCMS online editor by closing the browser may lock the content, requiring it to be unlocked to recover access and, 
                 therefore, losing any changes that may have been made previously.
                 
How do I integrate the content that appears in a different learning unit?	
  The Production LCMS application allows this to be done easily: 
    from the top menu, click on ""File"" then ""Import a LU"". 
    Following this, all of the activities present in this imported LU will be available for integration in the LU that you are designing.
    On the Web LCMS, you can extract animations to reuse them in other LUs. 
    To do this, go to the LU file that contains the desired animation and, from the actions menu, click on ""Extract an animation"". 
    The extracted animation becomes an independent object in your Project Library.
    
How do I integrate a new graphic design into my Web LCMS?	
  To import a new graphic design, go to ""Looks"" in your project on the Web LCMS. 
  There you will find various linguistic folders (FR, EN, etc.). 
  Import the archive containing your graphic design and place it in the folder corresponding to the language for which this graphic design will be used.
  
How do I move documents between projects on the Web LCMS?	"You can use the ""Duplicate within a project"" function on the Web LCMS. This allows you to create a copy of the LU or of the course within a different project. Note that the copy does not retain any potential log of publications on the LMS or of revisions that the original may have."
  What is the purpose of LCMS projects?	Projects can be created from the Manage Projects menu. They allow training content to be grouped according to training project. After that, you can create a folder tree for each project, enabling you to organise your training units and/or documents,
  "Following publication, only the ""No site"" value appears in the site selector. What should I do?"	"In order to be able to publish your content on your LMS, you must first select a site from the dropdown list. If you do not have a site on your LMS, it is necessary to select ""No site"", which allows you to progress with the publication process."
  Why is the LMS course into which I want to publish my content not offered as an option?	"You have a LMS base coupled with a TMS and there are two explanations for the behaviour noted:
  - if you are trying to publish a LU, this must first be added to a course on the LCMS, the course that will then be published on the LMS,
  - if you try to publish a LCMS course in a LMS course that is synchronised with the TMS that has already been published. It is only possible to publish a single course from the LCMS to the LMS course. A connection is then created between the two platforms to enable the single review of the course. If you want to publish a new course, you must create a new training action in your TMS and publish from your LCMS in the LMS that has been created."
  How do I renew the SSL certificate of the LMS?	To update the SSL certificate, please send it to use through your Support Area.
  Can I customise the LMS login page?	"The main modifications available are:
  - modify the colours, header background image and logo, via Administration > Display > Manage themes, then, once in the editor for the theme concerned, the ""Login screen"" tab,
  - add/hide the ""Forgotten password?"" button, via Administration > Technical settings > Security and passwords > ""Activate sending password"" (Yes/No),
  - add/hide the self-registration button, via Administration > Technical settings > Manage logins > Self-registration settings > ""Activate self-registration"",
  - add/hide the ""Login as guest"" button, via Administration > Technical settings > Manage logins > ""Authorise guest accounts (no login or password)"" (Yes/No)."
  How do I modify the default tab when logging into the LMS?	In order to modify the default tab when logging in, go to Administration > Display > Display options > Default tab.
  Is it possible to login to a specific site within the LMS?	"Yes, by using a dedicated homepage URL for the site in question. To obtain this URL, go to LMS Administration > Management > Sites > opposite the site in question there is an ""Actions"" button > Modify > note the value in the ""homepage URL"" line.
  By using this link to login to the LMS, the user will be directed to the site in question. This also relates to the LMS login page, which can be modified to the colours of the site in question, if necessary."
  How do I enable self-registration on the LMS?	"For this, go to LMS Administration > Technical settings > Manage logins > Self-registration settings. On this screen, you can set the way in which this feature is managed.
  You can also enable self-registration specific to a group or to a session:
  - self-registration in a group: go to the corresponding group file and click ""Modify"". Tick the box labelled ""Activate self-registration"" and copy the resulting link. Anybody using this link to create an account on the LMS will be automatically registered in the group (and any potential training sessions connected to this group),
  - self-registration in a session: go to the corresponding session file and click on the ""Modify"" icon in the ""Information"" sidebar. Activate the ""Self-registration"" setting and click OK. Drop down the ""Information"" sidebar and copy/paste the link behind the heading ""Click here"" (right click > Copy the link address). Anybody who uses this link to create an account on the LMS will be automatically registered in this session (and on the LMS site to which this session is associated, in case of multi-site LMS)."
  How do I translate the column headings for the CSV files used on the LMS?	"Translation is done manually as follows:
  - select the language into which your translations will be done using the selector located at the top right of the site,
  - go to Administration > Technical settings > Imports and exports > CSV import settings > CSV import field name settings,
  - on this screen, translate the headings. Repeat the process for as many languages as desired, taking care to select this language in advance using the dedicated selector."
  Can accounts with an Administrator profile view all of the LMS?	Administrators can view all of the LMS, especially if it is multi-site. If an Administrator is appointed as a site administrator, their visibility is restricted to only the content associated with this site (users, training sessions, etc.).
  How can I make a report available using a customised tab?	"Here is a step-by-step guide showing how to set up a report generated by a customised tab:
  - first, please modify an existing report template or create a new one from: Results > Analysis > Report templates > Add a template.
  - next, generate the report using simplified creation to obtain its permanent link: Results > Analysis > Simplified creation > Select your report template > Click OK to create your report. At the bottom of the preview page, copy the contents of the ""Permanent link"" field.
  - next, create your customised tab: Administration > Management > Menus and tabs. There, create a new tab or modify an existing tab and paste the permanent link that you previously copied. Choose the position of the tab in the menu bar, then click OK.
  - using a Super Administrator account, check that the tab is present and that it generates the report.
  Finally, you must approve the right for the profiles concerned to access the tab: Administration > Profiles and rights > Modify the rights of a profile > At the very bottom of the page, tick the right that corresponds to the newly-created tab for the profile or profiles that should have access, then save.

  The profiles concerned now have permission to access the tab. However, this must be activated in the various sessions from which it should be accessible. Settings for a session enable the tabs available on the screen to be displayed or hidden. You can activate this new tab for each session manually or by importing:
  - manually: open a session file, drop-down the ""Information"" sidebar at the bottom left, then click on ""Manage tabs"". Activate the tab in question, then click OK.
  - by importing: on the page Training > Sessions, click on Actions > Export > Exclude scheduling information: in the final column, ""tabs"", enter the title of the tab to be activated (see information that is already present for how to write this value). Next, import the file via Actions > Import.

  Next, log into one of the accounts in question to check that these settings are functioning properly."
  How do I download the content of a course from the LMS?	This action can only be done by a LMS Super Administrator account: go to Administration > Technical settings > Maintenance > Export a course. On the ext page, simply click on the course in question to download in the form of a .zip archive.
  Why should I set an Administrator for a LMS site?	"An Administrator (or similar) profile account can be appointed as the Administrator of a LMS site, if the platform has multi-site management. This can be set from LMS Administration > Management > Sites > Actions > Modify > select the account or accounts in question from the ""Site administrator"" list, then click OK.
  For the accounts in question, this restricts their visibility to the selected site only. In other words, a Site Administrator no longer has access to content related to other LMS sites.
  Furthermore, if these Administrators are also LCMS users, they will only be able to interact with their associated site.

  To remove an account from the list of Site Administrators, press Ctrl + left click on the heading of the account in question to unselect them, then click OK. Accounts removed in this way will once again have access to all LMS sites."
  How do I manage the languages available on the LMS?	"Languages available to be used on your LMS are available in Administration > Management > Languages. On this page, you can activate and deactivate the languages that can be used on the LMS.
  If one or more languages that you require are missing, please contact Customer Care to have them added. If the desired  translation does not exist, a service can be offered to obtain it."
  When creating a virtual class learning unit, can I use a solution other than that supplied by Talentsoft?	"Yes, when creating your LU you can select the option ""Link to an external class"". On the next page, you can integrate a link to an external solution (Zoom, etc.)."
  Who has access to the recording of a virtual class?	"This depends on the method used to create the virtual class: in the case of a virtual class that launches directly (accessible from the ""Virtual Class"" tab), it is the host who creates the virtual class.
  In the case of a virtual class created using a learning unit within a session, two scenarios are possibles:
  - the LU is scheduled: the host is the trainer (among those registered for the session) who was appointed as trainer for this virtual class session during scheduling,
  - the LU is not scheduled: the host is one of the trainers registered for the session who created the virtual class."
  What is the maximum number of participants for virtual classes?	The maximum capacity for a virtual class is 50 users. 
  What is the best way to manage my LMS user licences?	"You can manage your account as you wish and can even exceed the number of licences contracted. This is not a limited number. At the time of invoicing, we take the day of the month on which your number of active users was at its highest. If you exceed your threshold, you will be invoiced for additional accounts.
  In addition, a multi-profile account is deemed to be a single account and, therefore, only one licence is used.

  Do not hesitate to contact your Talentsoft commercial representative for further information concerning invoicing for your services."
  A LMS user can no longer login following several unsuccessful attempts. How do I unlock their account?	"Too many unsuccessful login attempts will lock the account for 24 hours.
  You can view locked accounts from this page: Administration > Technical settings > Maintenance > Accounts locked by the anti-intrusion system. Use the button at the bottom of the page to unlock the most recent accounts affected and to delete the list on this page."
  Can I edit the login for LMS accounts?	Editing a login is not possible on the LMS, either manually using the interface or by CSV import because it is the account's unique identifier. The only way of making such a change is to use the LMS web services. The Talentsoft Customer Care service is not responsible for such changes, which are very significant and likely to result in undesirable side effects.
  How do I automatically log a Trainee out of the LMS in case of inactivity?	"You can define a browser session period, a period during which the user does not have to log back in if the browser is closed. Once this period expires, the user will have to log back into the LMS.

  For this, go to LMS Administration > Technical settings > Manage logins. You will find a field labelled ""Session time in seconds"" allowing you to define this period during which it is not necessary to log back in after leaving the platform (browser or tab being closed).
  You can also authorise ongoing logins through the setting of the same name. This enables a box labelled ""Stay logged in"" to be displayed on the LMS login screen which, if ticked, enables the user to remain logged in to the platform indefinitely, even if the browser is closed or the computer is shut down.

  Finally, these settings do not result in Trainees being automatically logged out if they are browsing the LMS or e-learning content."
  How do I force a password change following the first LMS login?	"From Administration > Management, Login event, you can add a page following login with the ""Modify your account"" action. Next, tick ""Password"" and ""Compulsory"", then in the ""Display"" dropdown menu, select ""If the account password was created or edited by another account""."
  What is the storage policy for user data on the LMS?	"Any account deleted from the LMS is permanently deleted from the database. 
  Data will only be retained in back-up images (30 days, rolling).  This data cannot be accessed without technical action to restore it, which is only carried out at your request within the context of a service (for example, in case of the accidental deletion of courses, users, etc.).
  Also consider keeping your test database up to date so that data deleted in production does not remain in it."
  Can I send a LMS user their password?	"For security reasons, the password can only appear unencrypted in an email if it is sent when the user's account is created. If a template email containing the variable !%password%! is sent to a user after creation of their account, the password is replaced by ""********"".
  There are three options open to you:
  - ask the user to reset their password from the LMS login page using the ""Forgotten password?"" link (if this link is active),
  - as Administrator, manually edit the account password and send it to its owner,
  - edit or create a template email to replace the variable !%password%! with !%reset_pass_link%! (reset password link)."
  What is the difference between an expired account and a deactivated account on the LMS?	"There are four account statuses: ​
  Not yet active: the account has a start date in the future,​
  Active: the account has a start date in the past and an end date in the future,​
  Expired: the account has an end date in the past,​
  Deactivated: the account's ""active"" field is set to NO.​

  Exceeding the end date does not impact accounts' ""active"" fields and they are not automatically deactivated."
  Who are the group delegates?	"A Trainee can be appointed as delegate for their group. A delegate can view the results of other members of the group, in the same way as a Trainer.
  The delegate can be selected using the edit group interface and by CSV import: in the account import file, locate the ""delegate"" column and, on the line corresponding to the account in question, add the name of the group for which they are to be delegate.
  Note that a delegate must be registered for the same training sessions as the other Trainees so as to be able to view the latter's results."
  A Trainee completed a learning unit, but it was not validated. Why?	"There are several possible reasons for this. Here are the most common:
  - ""Completed, not validated"" status: the validation score was not achieved or the LU does not generate a score. Please check the settings for the course and/or learning unit.
  - ""In progress"" status: it is likely that an activity was not viewed by the Trainee. If your content was created using Production LCMS or another tool, check that all activities can be viewed by the Trainee. Please also check whether the activities that may not have been viewed are defined as optional (with LCMS Prod: browsing coefficient = 0). In this way, the fact of not having viewed these optional activities does not prevent completion of the LU.
  - ""Not started"" status: please check that your LU generates tracking and that at least one activity (for example, the first one) is not optional."
  On the test LMS, the content of learning units is replaced by homologation content. Why?	This is completely normal. When copying from the production LMS to a test LMS, the course structure is retained (number of LUs and titles, settings, etc.), but the LU content is not transferred for performance reasons.
  How do I automate sending achievement certificates to Trainees?	"Requirement: have a template email and a template report to send to the Trainees. This content can be created from Results Analysis > Template emails/Template reports.

  The simplest method is to create an automatic event that triggers the sending of an email, containing the certificate as an attachment, to the Trainees who complete or approve a course. To do this, go to Results > Analysis > Manage event scheduling > Create a schedule > Add an event.

  On this screen:
  - Name the event,
  - Action: course approved or course completed, depending on desired condition of sending,
  - Selection of course or courses for which completion/approval triggers the sending of the email,
  - Selection of report template to be used,
  - Selection of email template to be used,
  - Selection of course related to the email sent,
  - Approve the event then the schedule containing the event.

  It is easy to test that these settings are operating correctly by completing/approving the target course using a Trainee account with a valid email address then viewing the content received."
  What are the viewing rules for Trainer profiles?	"On the LMS, visibility of Trainer accounts (or similar profile) over other accounts is specific. Here are the standard visibility rules:
  - with regard to Trainees: a Trainer can only view the Trainees if they created their account themselves and registered it for the same training sessions OR if they have at least one group in common and are registered for the same training sessions OR if the ""Trainers view all trainees in the session"" setting (Administration > Profiles and rights > Advanced options) is active.
  - with regard to other Trainers: a Trainer cannot view their peers, unless they created their account themselves."
  "What is the purpose of the ""Associate"" action for user selection, report templates or email templates?"	This option enables you to set which profile is able to use the content and where on the platform (which session, which page). If a user does not have access to the content (report, email template, user selection), first check that the content is associated to them.
  If a Trainee makes several attempts at a learning unit, what information will be included in the LMS report?	"That depends on the context. Here are some common examples. If the Trainee has made one or more attempts:
  - If the LU is has the status ""In progress"": the most recent score achieved will be included in the report,
  - If the LU has the status ""Completed, not approved"": the score obtained upon completion of the LU will be included in the report,
  - If the LU has the status ""Approved"": the score obtained upon validation of the LU will be included in the report,
  - If the LU has the status ""Completed, not approved"" then ""Approved"" (or the inverse): the score obtained upon validation of the LU will be included in the report,

  If the Trainee has made several attempts:
  - One of which has the status ""Approved"": information concerning this approved attempt will appear in the report,
  - Several of which have the status ""Approved"": information concerning the most recent approved attempt will appear in the report,"
  How do I import results into the LMS?	"On the LMS, importing results is done for each learning unit separately. This is the method:
  - create a selection of users (via Results > Analysis > Create a selection of users) enabling you to search for thee people to whom this importing of results relates,
  - perform the search and select the accounts concerned. If all are relevant, do not select any and click on Actions > Import results > select the LU concerned by the import and click OK,
  - on this page, click on ""Download the template"" to obtain a file that is already completed, into which you only have to add the ""Score"", ""Time spent"", ""Date attempted"" and ""Completed"" (yes/no) columns. Column H onwards is optional and you can delete them if you do not intend to use them,
  - on the LMS, import this file from the screen from which it was downloaded. Your results are now available on the LMS."
  Why are the responses given by the Trainee not visible on the Results page?	"Currently, only LUs produced using the Talentsoft LCMS permit expected responses and the responses given by the Trainee to be recorded on the LMS.
  If you want a non-Talentsoft LU to send details of responses to the Talentsoft LMS, this should be submitted in the following data fields:
  - cmi.interactions.n.correct_response_text = Expected response
  - cmi.interactions.n.student_response_text.n.pattern=Response given by the trainee

  Please contact your service provider or the developer of your design tool."
  How do I use selections of users in the LMS search engines?	"Go to Administration > Display > Search engines. Select the search engine concerned then click on ""List of saved selections"". Tick the required selections and click OK.
  These selections can now be used on the screens in question."
  Can I hide or lock learning units during a session?	"On the LMS session sheet, several settings are available in the ""Information"" sidebar, including the setting ""A learning unit is"". To access it, click on the edit icon located in the top right corner of the ""Information"" sidebar, then select the value that matches the desired behaviour. For example: ""hide if completed"", ""greyed out and inactive if completed"", etc."
  How do I translate the titles of sessions, courses and learning units on the LMS?	"These elements can only be translated on the LMS.
  For sessions: select the desired language for the LMS using the selector located at the top right of the screen. Next, translate the title of the session into the language previously selected. Now, by changing the language of the platform, the translated title is displayed.
  For courses and learning units: go to the course editing screen and select the language into which the information will be translated using the selector at the top right of the editor, then click on ""OK"". On the next screen, translate the various elements, then click OK.

  Note that if information for a session/course/LU is not translated into the language selected on the LMS, the source information will be displayed by default (potentially in a language that is different to that selected by the user on the LMS)."
  How to I prevent access to a session outside of the start and end dates?	"From the description sheet for the session in question, click on the edit button located opposite the session title (""pencil"" icon), then activate the setting ""Prevent access by trainees outside of these dates""."
  "Can a session be associated with multiple LMS sites?
  "	No, a session can only be linked to a single site on the LMS.
  What is the difference duplication in association with and independent of a session?​	"Duplication in association (default when creating a session) enables the session to be duplicated and the course or courses contained within the original session to be associated with it. Any change made to these courses affects both the original session and its copy.​
  ​
  Independent duplication allows a copy of a session AND the courses contained within this session to be created. Editing the course copied in this way does not affect the course contained within the original session.​"
  A Trainee encounters a locked screen with a padlock on an exercise. Why?	"The appearance of this ""padlock"" is linked to a setting that applies to this activity that restricts the number of attempts available to the Trainee. Once these attempts have been made, the screen is locked to prevent new entries in the exercise. On the LCMS, check the setting ""The Trainee can do the exercise"" in the window ""Advice in case of error"" for the activity concerned. This lock can also occur when the trainee has exceeded the allocated time for the LU or for the activity in question.
  In addition, it is better to deactivate the ""back"" button on the next activity to prevent the user returning to the locked activity and getting stuck."
  Can a Trainee restart an Assessment immediately or later?	No, this type of LU can only accept one series of responses and it is not possible to reset them.
  How do I import e-learning content that is greater than 32 MB to the LMS?	"If you have Talentsoft LCMS, import your content above then publish it to the LMS.

  Otherwise, you must upload this content to the LMS FTP server, then import it into the course in question. This is the process to be followed:
  - check that you have the credentials for the FTP area linked to your LMS. If you do not have them or if you have forgotten them, contact Customer Care who will send them to you,
  - log in to the FTP server using dedicated software, such as Filezilla,
  - add your content to the server root,
  - on the LMS, in the course in question (or when creating a new course) add ""An e-learning module"" type LU,
  - on the next screen, headed ""Import a course"", select ""Integrate a course stored via FTP"",
  - on the next screen, select the content in question and check that the ""Import"" action is selected from the ""Action"" dropdown menu, then click OK,
  - the import occurs and your content is integrated into the course in the form of a learning unit. Remember to check changes made to the course."
  "How do I use the ""Appraisal by a trainer"" learning unit?"	"This is how to implement this type of LU (the first three points can be carried out on the LCMS or the LMS):
  - create a standard e-learning LU containing questionnaires and other text fields that the Trainer will use in their Appraisal,
  - publish this LU to a LMS course (other than the course offered to the Trainee),
  - add a ""Appraisal by trainer"" type LU to the course on which the Trainee is registered on the LMS,
  - select the previously published e-learning LU from the ""Learning unit offered to the trainer"" dropdown menu (this menu does not exist on the LCMS, you must edit the LU on the LMS),
  - next, the Trainer goes to the ""Results"" page for the Trainee to be appraised and clicks on the ""Appraise"" button, located opposite the ""Appraisal by trainer"" LU contained within the course.


  Next, the appraisal information provided by the Trainer becomes accessible through the Trainee's Results page and through the issuing of a CSV report based on the ""CSV Question"" or ""CSV Response"" template."
  Can I delete a training action that is linked to a plan?	Training actions linked to an approved plan cannot be deleted. The plan must be switched to an earlier status to be able to perform this action.
  Why can I not edit the theme of a training action?	The theme of a training action cannot be edited once sessions and registrations are linked to it. In this case, it is necessary to deactivate the training action and to create a new one linked to the theme in question.
  How and why do I deactivate a training action?	"A training action is activated or deactivated using the ""Active"" box, located within the description of the action, or using the ""active"" column in the ""Training actions V2"" import (values: ""true"" or ""false"").
  Deactivating a training action does not prevent it from being used. This refers to information given for information purposes, such as signifying that this training action is no longer current."
  How do I restrict visibility of training actions?	"You can restrict visibility of training actions in the catalogue according to employees' KPPs (location, entity, etc.).​

  To do this, click on the ""Visibility of actions"" quicklook within the description of a training action and complete the KPPs for the employees concerned. A complete guide to this matter is available on the Talentsoft Community."
  How do I link a training action duration that is greater than the daily working duration on our platform?	"Using the ""Training actions V2"" import, there is a column headed ""durationperday"". This column, which is to be completed using whole numbers, enables you to specify the duration of the training action in hours and replaces the default working day duration that is set for your platform. This enables you to schedule training days automatically without the number of days being more than you actually need."
  Can I delete a training action?	"A training action can be deleted under these conditions:
  - no session is associated with it,
  - there are no requirements linked to the action,
  - the action is not linked to a plan."
  How is the estimated time required for my blended training action calculated? 	For Blended actions, the estimated time required is calculated automatically according to the duration of each LU that makes up this action.
  How do I display or hide a training category?	"This is done from Administration > Reference data > Training categories. 
  Tick or untick the ""Active"" box for each value that you want to see appear or not on your platform."
  "Why is the ""Cycle type"" dropdown menu empty?"	"You can update the list of cycle types using Administration > Reference data > Cycle type. 
  Here, you can enter the various values that you want to find in the dropdown menu. "
  How do I manage the library of training action themes?	"Training themes are managed via the ""Training catalogue"" KPP. You can populate this KPP to create themes and sub-themes which can then be selected when creating a training action."
  How do I archive group training requirements?	Currently, it is not possible to archive group training requirements.
  "Can I hide the archived requirements in the ""Their training"" widget?"	"Display settings for requirements according to their status only affects the ""My training"" widget, accessible as an employee.
  The ""Their training"" widget, which can be viewed by Managers, displays all the requirements of people on the team, regardless of the status selected. This is a standard feature of the application."
  How do I manage visibility of the group training requirements?	Visibility of the group requirements is managed by authorisation. A group requirement created by person A is only visible by person B if A falls within the scope of B's authorisations.
  Why can I not find an employee's requirement issued in a form?	"If you cannot find the requirement of an employee made in a form (in the Training component), the first thing to check is the status of the form. Only requirements issued in a form that has Approved status appear in the Individual training requirements menu.

  Note: all requirements appear in reports and in the Individual Requirements export, with no distinction made between the status of the form in which the requirement was issued."
  What are the various methods of gathering training requirements?	"These are the various methods of gathering training requirements:
  - Issuing a requirement during an interview campaign,
  - An employee issuing a requirement using an open access form,
  - An individual requirement being issued by a manager through the training catalogue,
  - Gathering individual/group requirements in real time by the training department,
  - Issuing individual and group requirements across the training cycle."
  What is the difference between individual and group requirements?	"Individual requirements generally originate from annual appraisal interviews and requirement gathering campaigns and express the training requirements of a group of known, named individuals.

  Group requirements requested by a manager, HR or a training manager express training requirements for a given number of ""anonymous"" individuals. What is significant here is to have an idea of the number of people requiring training on a particular action so as to obtain an overall perspective of the cost and the training load pertaining to the training plan.

  Note: A training plan is constructed around a set of individual and group requirements. However, it might also be drafted in full around a particular type of requirement."
  What is the difference between a budgeted requirement and a non-budgeted requirement?	"A ""budgeted"" requirement corresponds to a requirement that is added to a plan that is in preparation.
  Adding requirements to a plan that is being delivered constitutes ""non-budgeted"" requirements.

  Only budgeted requirements are accounted for in the provisional budget for the plan."
  Can I delete a training requirement?	"No. Once a requirement is created it cannot be deleted. However, you can archive it using the actions menu located on the training actions summary screen.
  Customer Care does not process requests for deletion, except for when they concern the GDPR right to be forgotten."
  Under what conditions is a training requirement displayed in the back office?	"If the requirement was issued using a form (as part of a campaign or open access), the form must be approved for the training requirement to be submitted to the back office.

  You must also have permission to view the employee in question or to have the right to bypass the visibility rules to view the requirement in the back office.

  In addition, only non-archived requirements are visible in standard display mode. Archived requirements can be found using a specific search."
  In the catalogue, can I restrict access to some training actions using roles and rights?	Currently, you can only restrict this access by KPP.
  How do I manage visibility within the Training Catalogue?	"There are various ways of managing the visibility of training actions within the catalogue
  - Restricting visibility of a catalogue theme according to key properties (Intelligence > Visibility management > Tree library > Training Catalogue),
  - Restricting visibility of a training action according to KPP (Training Module > Catalogue> Training Actions > Action Visibility quick look),
  - Restricting visibility of a training session according to KPP (Training Module > Management > Sessions > Session Visibility quick look > ""Session visibility in the training catalogue"" setting),

  For restricting visibility by KPP to affect your catalogue, you must activate it from the Intelligence menu > Visibility management > Contextualisation. 

  A guide to visibility management within the Training module is available on the Talentsoft Comnunity."
  Why does a user who is not affected by a training action have access to it in the Catalogue?	"There are several possible explanations:
  - the training action is displayed in the ""My catalogue"" view: this user has one of the KPPs that restrict access to the training action,
  - the training action is displayed in the ""My scope's catalogue"" view: an account that appears in the user authorisation list can view the training action. Therefore, the user inherits this visibility in this catalogue view. For example, you can deactivate the ""FO Training"" module for the authorisation list in question. In this way, your user will no longer inherit visibility of the training actions that can be accessed by the accounts affected by this authorisation list."
  Can I customise the fields that appear in the Training Catalogue?	"Currently, it is only possible to edit the headings of the fields that appear, using Administration > Manage languages > Resources.

  This page enables you search for the titles used on the platform and to define the custom titles."
  Why can I not register for a current training session through the Catalogue?	"There is a difference between blended and face-to-face training sessions:
  - face-to-face training: it is only possible to register for future sessions (start date in the future),
  - blended training: it is possible to register for future and current sessions (start date in the past and end date in the future)."
  Can I edit the provisional cost associated with a training requirement?	"Training requirements inherit the costs added to the training actions with which they are associated.
  If you want to edit a cost that appears with a requirement, you can do so either by importing or, if the cost cannot be edited by importing, by editing the cost of the training action and creating a new requirement that applies the updated training cost.
  The following costs can be edited by importing: trainee transport, food and accommodation costs, actual cost, salary cost, external trainer salary costs, equipment costs, trainer transport, food and accommodation costs, cost of hiring the room, cost of delivering materials.
  Files for importing are: ""Links between individual requirements and training plans"" and ""Links between group requirements and training plans""."
  "What does the phrase ""reference cost"" mean?"	"The ""Reference cost"" tick box allows you to indicate which teaching cost should be used to calculate the provisional total of a training plan in preparation. Only one teaching cost can be marked as being the reference cost."
  What is the cost calculation difference between INTER and INTRA training actions?	"The cost of an INTER training action is calculated by multiplying the cost by the number of trainees paying the session fees.
  In contrast, the cost of an INTRA training action is et, regardless of the number of registrations."
  Why are the totals for my spent and confirmed budgets different?	"The confirmed budget corresponds to the total registration costs that are considered to be ""confirmed"".
  The spent budget corresponds to the total registration costs that are  considered to be ""spent"".

  The corresponding settings can be accessed via Intelligence > Object setting > object: Registrations > settings: Status types. On this screen, the columns ""Consider a registration as Performed"" and ""Consider a registration as Confirmed"" allow you to define the statuses corresponding to each type of registration.
  Therefore, these totals may be different depending on the settings selected."
  "What is the purpose of the field ""Pay session costs""?"	"Calculating session costs does not take into account any registrations for which this box, ""Pay session costs"", is ticked.
  If an employee is absent, the registration can therefore be excluded from the cost calculation for the session by unticking the box."
  How do I manage changing costs related to training actions?	"For a training action, if the educational cost or the cost of training materials changes, it is strongly recommended that you create a new action with a new effective date, rather than editing an existing cost.

  The new cost will only affect the sessions for which the start date is the same as or later than the effective date of the new cost and for which the service provider is identical to that indicated on the cost in the training action."
  Why can the provisional budget for my plan not be edited after I have added requirements?	Budgets for a plan are automatically updated every night. You can force this update via Select an action > Recalculate budgets.
  Under what conditions can someone self-register for a training cycle from the Catalogue?	"Self-registration for a training cycle is possible from the catalogue under these conditions:
  - the cycle has scheduled sessions,
  - the sessions are set up to allow self-registration,
  - the sessions are set up to be visible in My Talentsoft.

  At the point of registering for a cycle, the various training actions are offered and, for each one, sessions are available. Therefore, in reality, registering for a training cycle constitutes one or more registrations for sessions arising from training actions linked to the cycle.

  It is not possible to register for a cycle using the Training back office, although it is possible to register for various sessions in the training actions that make up the cycle."
  Is it possible to edit the type of training (face-to-face, blended) of an existing training action?	"To convert a face-to-face training action to a blended one, you can use the Training actions V2 file and, in the ""LmsPartner"" column, replace the value ""NoLms"" with ""TS_LMS"" for the training actions in question. Please note that this operation is possible in this direction (NoLms > TS_LMS) but not in the other (TS_LMS > NoLms). Therefore, a blended training action cannot be converted into a face-to-face action.

  When importing the file, the following changes are made:
  - the training actions in question are changed to blended training actions and the corresponding courses are created on the LMS, allowing content to be published from the LCMS. This synchronisation takes place automatically with the batches in place between TMS and LMS or manually using the ""Synchronisation"" button that appears in the ""Training content"" quick look for the trainign actions,
  - sessions in progress at the point of importing become blended sessions and can be synchronised manually using the corresponding button that appears on their file or automatically with the TMS/LMS synchronisation batches,
  - sessions created after the import are automatically synchronised with the LMS."
  How do I batch link registrations to a plan?	"You can perform this batch action by importing, using the file ""Training session registrations"". To link a registration to a plan, complete the column ""trainingwishclientcode"" (code for the requirement linked to the registration) and ""trainingplanclientcode"" (plan code). 
  "
  How do I manage completed training that appears on employees' MiniCVs?	"Training, either within or outside the company, can be created on the MiniCV in two ways:
  - using the ""Completed training"" import,
  - automatically, when a registration for training managed by the TMS module becomes ""Completed"".

  If a line was created by importing the ""Completed training"" file, you can:
  - delete it: using the ""Completed training"" file. Export it and enter the value ""delete"" in the ""action"" column for the line or lines concerned. Import the file to perform the deletion. You need only retain the lines to be edited in the import file so as to avoid creating duplicates in employees' MiniCVs.
  - edit it: using the ""Completed training manually entered"" file. Export this file and edit the corresponding line (without editing the value in the column ""training_code"") then import the file to apply the changes.

  If lines were automatically created following a completed registration, the line can be deleted from the MiniCV provided that the corresponding registration is deleted from the back office, with possible repercussions in terms of monitoring the budget, for example."
  "Why do imported training requirements not appear in the ""My training"" widget?"	"Consider checking the source of the requirement using the ""Individual training requirements"" export: 

  If the source is not:

  MY_TS
    TS_EVALUATION
    TS_DEVELOPPEMENT
    TALENT_REVIEW
    TS_MANAGERREQUEST
    REGISTRATIONSOURCE_TRAININGMATCH
    the requirement is visible in the back office but not in the front office as only the sources listed above allow the visibility of requirements to be activated using the Object parameters menu."
  What is the difference between the Completed training and Attendance details quick looks?	"The ""Completed training"" quick look is available for blended registrations and allows information generated on the LMS to be viewed (approval, score obtained, actual and reserved durations, etc.).

  The ""Attendance details"" quick look presumes that there is a schedule in the ""Time and place"" quick look for the session and allows registration attendance information to be viewed."
  How are the registrations that are automatically offered for a session (push) determined?	"For a trainee to be recommended automatically:
  - There must be a requirement in a current plan (approved plan and current date),
  - The requirement must not be archived,
  - The requirement must be issued for an action or for the training theme,
  - The requirement status must match the requirement statuses defined as being offered for registration (see Intelligence > Training requirements object > Status types),
  - If the trainee was already registered for the same theme or for a session within the same training action, they will not be re-recommended, unless the corresponding setting in Intelligence > Registrations object, allows it."
  Under what conditions does a registration apply to the MiniCV?	"Once registration for training has been switched to ""Completed"" and attendance to ""Present"", the training in question is added to the employee's MiniCV."
  "The time counter in the ""Completed training"" quick look does not update after the training is approved. Why?"	"The value that appears in this quick look is the same as the ""Duration reserved"" (for training), which itself is the same as the estimated training time given for the training action and the session. For blended training, this estimated duration is the same as the ""estimated time"" for training given in the training units published in the course on the LMS.
  Once the TMS registration is approved, if the ""Completed training"" quick look is not updated with the reserved/estimated duration for the training, this usually means that your registration was created on the TMS before the LMS course was updated (and therefore before an estimated training duration was generated on the TMS).
  If this situation occurs, you must update the value of the duration reserved manually or by import:
  - manually: by editing the ""Hours completed by training category"" tables (found in the ""Completed training"" and ""Edit training categories"" quick look detail (found in the registration detail), with the expected value. 
  - by import: using the ""Training session registrations"" file. Fill in the ""fulltime_*"" and ""realized_fulltime_*"" columns (where * relates to the training category in question). Then, import the file, which will allow the duration reserved associated with the registration to be updated.

  These changes also allow a training category to be linked with the registrations (which cannot be linked without a training duration reserved) and to calculate the costs that depend on this duration reserved (for example, salary cost for internal trainers).

  In summary, to protect yourself from such a situation, create your blended registrations after completing the LMS training units course."
  How do I create or edit a Word+ template?	"Creating or editing Word+ templates is in the hands of our clients and Customer Care is not involved in these matters pertaining to the use of Word. For any delegation requirements, please subscribe to a Content+ Advanced Services contract.
  If you encounter problems using this feature, Customer Care is happy to help you."
  "To which person(s) does the ""Initiator"" column in the change of status notifications settings refer?"	"This ""initiator"" column refers to any person who created the action as a recipient of the notification.

  For example, within the context of a notification sent upon the creation of a registration with the status ""Registered"", the initiator may be:
  - the employee, if they self-registered,
  - the manager, if they registered a member of their team via the catalogue,
  - a training manager, if they registered an employee using the Training back office.

  With regard to a notification setting upon registration, for example, the initiator is the person that created the registration. If this person leaves and someone cancels a registration, the initiator is not updated and the person that created the registration receives the email. "
  Why does editing the status of a registration by importing not trigger the sending of a notification by email?	"Notifications about changes of status, set up from the Intelligence menu, do not generate emails when the change was made by importing. The system needs to record a manual or automatic change of status (""Offered"" to ""Approved"", for example) for a notification to be triggered.

  In contrast, you can create notifications via Administration > Notifications, enabling you regularly to search for people meeting certain criteria (for example: a person with a registration with the status ""Registered"") and to send them the selected email. The only difference from training is that it is not sent immediately."
  What do the various phases of a training plan correspond to?	"(Add the table from page 16 of the costs guide and add a specific column for sessions/registrations, refer to: https://help.talentsoft.com/s/article/Quelles-sont-les-diff%C3%A9rentes-%C3%A9tapes-du-plan-de-formation-1528095742864)

  The various phases of a plan are:
  - Provisional: the plan is being drafted and has not started (start date not passed),
  - Awaiting approval: the plan is in the process of approval and has not started, OR the plan is being drafted and has started,
  - Awaiting implementation: the plan is approved and has not started,
  - Implementation: the plan is approved and implementation has started (start date passed)
  - Completed: the plan end date is passed.

  Impacts:
  When the plan is in the ""Provisional"", ""Awaiting implementation"" or ""Awaiting approval"" phases:
  - The requirements added to the plan are ""budgeted"",
  - When registering for a session, no employee is suggested,
  - No link can be made between requirements and session registrations.

  When the plan is in the ""Implementation"" phase:
  - The requirements added to the plan populate the ""non-budgeted"" budget,
  - Employees that issued an approved requirement for a training action that is part of the plan will be suggested when registering for a session including this training action (push),
  - Upon registration, they can be linked to the issued requirement."
  Can I edit the provisional budget for an approved training plan?	Once the training plan is approved and in the process of implementation, the provisional budget is fixed and can no longer be edited.
  How do I export the cost breakdown for sessions and registrations?	"You can use the following export files to do this, available from Administration > Exports:
  - Breakdown of session costs
  - Breakdown of registration costs"
  "Why is the ""Requirements in the plan"" data source partially empty when exported?"	This occurs if your database allows registration plans without a linked requirement to be linked to. The empty portions that appear in this report are in fact unnominated requirements created when a registration without a linked requirement is linked to a plan, this is the platform's normal behaviour.
  When creating a blended session, why is there no destination LMS site?	The user must have an administrator and/or trainer profile account, registered to the site in question, to be able to select this site when creating a session on the TMS.
  "Why do I receive the message ""The training content does not contain any synchronous learning units for scheduling."" when scheduling a blended session?"	"This message is displayed under the following conditions:

  on the LMS, you have not published synchronous learning units (virtual class, classroom training) in the course linked to the training action,
  if these LUs were published on the LMS, the training action was not refreshed on the TMS. To do this, you need to open the ""Course plan"" quick look for the action in question to enable information to be synchronised with the LMS, after which, scheduling will be possible."
  How do I link a session to a plan?	"You cannot link a session to a plan manually. You can link registrations to a plan, which will have the effect of making the session available in the ""Plan sessions"" quick look."
  Can I delete a Training Match rule? 	"Training Match rules that have already been implemented cannot be deleted, only archived. 
  Only rules with draft or active status that have not been triggered can be deleted. "
  Why do I not have access to Training Match?	"You do not have access to Training Match following its activation by Talentsoft because a right is missing from your role(s).
  Please add the right ""Training Match: Manage training strategies"" to the role(s) that are to set up Training Match, from Administration > Roles and rights.

  If Training Match is not yet activated on your database, please ask Talentsoft Customer Care."
  I created and activated a rule with an effective date of today, but the target population has not been registered. Why?	"Training Match is executed every day at around 5.00 a.m. (French time), by default.

  If you activate a rule on the same day as its implementation start date and the daily execution time is passed, you must wait for the next morning for the first registrations to be made."
  Can I use Training Match to manage batch registration for the training?	Training Match is not designed to offer batch registration management. We do not recommend that you use it for this purpose.
  "How do I hide registrations and requirements on the ""My training"" widget?"	"You can set up the display of ""My training"" requirements and registrations from Intelligence > Object parameters > Registrations (or Training requirements) >  Status types. 

  This screen allows you to set whether the object should appear in the ""My training"" widget for each requirement/registration status. "
  "How do I allow registration statuses and requirements to be edited in the ""My training"" and ""Their training"" widgets?"	"This setting requires the process of creating status charts to be understood. A complete guide to this matter is available on the Talentsoft Community.

  Subsequently, if you want to allow users to be able to edit registration statuses in their ""My training"" widget themselves, here are the various charts to add, depending on the source of the registrations in question: https://talentsoft.atlassian.net/wiki/spaces/SPT/pages/1396342901/La+modification+des+tats+des+besoins+inscriptions+dans+le+widget+Formation"
  "What is the display order of registrations in the ""My training"" widget and can it be changed? "	"Registrations on ""in progress"" sessions are displayed according to session end date. For example: a registration for a session that ends on 15 July of the current year is positioned before a registration for a session with an end date of 30 October."
  "When logging in as an employee, the ""My training"" widget does not appear. Why?"	"Some pages and widgets are not visible when you take control of another user's account.

  Your authorisations stay the same when you take control of a different account and the content may be different depending on your roles and rights."
  I want to schedule a virtual class LU for the morning and a face-to-face LU for the afternoon. The tool does not allow me to. Why?	Currently, a LU is considered to be a full day in the LMS so it is not possible to schedule two LUs for the same day in the TMS.
  "Why is the ""Attendance details"" quick look not accessible?"	"The ""Attendance details"" quick look is active provided there is a schedule for your session in the ""Time and place"" quick look.

  Under these conditions, ""Attendance details"" can be used for information about trainees' attendance on their training."
  Since 1 January 2021, some learning units no longer display correctly. Why?	"Until 31 December 2020, browsers allowed you to use Flash technology. From 1 January 2021, this technology has been removed from modern browsers.
  It may be that LUs experiencing this issue require Flash to be read correctly. Please check whether this is the case and, if it is, redevelop them to make them fully compatible with HTML5 technology (in other words: delete any content that requires Flash)."
  How do I populate the provisional salary cost using group requirements?	"From the plan to which the group requirement is attached, select the requirement in question and you will find an ""Average hourly rate"" field that you can complete.

  If the options for the plan allow it, this AHR populates the provisional budget for the group requirement that you are editing. It will be multiplied by the provisional number of trainees then by the estimated training duration.

  It is possible that this field is not displayed on your database, if so, please contact Customer Care to have this field added."
  Are multilingual LMS report templates possible?	"They are possible in the following way:
  - create your PDF report template in one language,
  - edit the LMS language, selecting a target translation language,
  - edit your report template by translating the various elements (text, images, etc.) into the target language,
  - save it. Now you can generate your report in either language depending on the language selected by the user when generating their report.

  Note that the name of the report template is not translated, this is shared by all languages."
  "An ""A link"" type LU displays an error page when I open it. Why?
  "	"This behaviour generally means that the target site is set up to prevent it being opened in a ""contained"" way within another site (in this case, the LMS).

  If you want to make a link to this site available on the LMS through a LU, you must use ""A webpage"" type LUs and insert the link to the site in question into them, setting it to open in a new window."
  Why is the time that my Trainees spend in virtual class not recorded correctly?	"To ensure that the time spent on Virtual Class learning units is recorded correctly, the Trainee must close their LU using the dedicated close button, located in the top right corner of the window.
  If the browser (or the tab) is closed, a warning message asks the user to confirm this action. If this closure is approved, the time spent on this Virtual Class LU is not saved on the LMS."
  How do I add an additional field to a TMS object?	"There are two steps to add new fields to Training objects (plan, training action, session, registration, etc.):

  1. Creating the field in question if it is a customised field:
  - go to Intelligence > Object parameters and select the object to be set > Additional fields,
  - create your field.

  2. Adding it to the desired screen: contact Talentsoft Customer Care, stating the relevant information:
  - adding a standard field: send us the name of the field, the page in question and the desired position,
  - adding a customised field: send us the code for the field, the page in question and the desired position."
  
}.